

FELIPE PIZARRO

Front End Developer

ABOUT ME

Entry level Front End Developer from Nucamp Coding Bootcamp based in Milan, Italy. Currently I have a basic level in React, Javascript, Bootstrap, JAVA and with knowledge of MySQL.

I also have a degree in journalism and have two years of experience as a Video Editor.

CONTACT ME

felipepizarro.com linkedin.com/in/felipepizarrodev +39 375 692 6649 fpizarro.ux@gmail.com Milano, Italy

LANGUAGES

English: C1TOEFL English Test

Italian: B2 Spanish: Native

EXPERIENCE

2022- JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Sisal Academy

I was selected together with 24 other students to enter Sisal/Modis Academy, and intense 6 week program to study the basics of Sisal's technologies: JAVA and MySQL as the main focus.

2021-2022 JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp

I developed an Expense Tracker with React and Bootstrap guided by tutorials as my graduation project. I used a mobile responsive approach, updating the state of the app through React.

2019 - 2020 **VIDEO EDITOR**

ALMA Observatory / Santiago de Chile

Video editing, creation of scripts and voice over for Instagram stories and posts. Educational content about astronomy and ALMA's research.

EDUCATIONS

2021 - 2022 FULL STACK WEB + MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp

A six month program on four technologies. Bootstrap, React, React Native and Node. Weekly workshops separated by groups where we nexecuted coding tasks and challenges.

2015 - 2020 SOCIAL COMMUNICATIONS DEGREE

Universidad UNIACC | Universidad de Sevilla (One Semester)

A four year studies program focused on media and communications. I won a scolarship to study abroad for one semester at Spain. One year of internal internship doing a docummentary, NGO communications and newspaper contribution.

PRO SKILLS

React	4 months	Photoshop	2 years
Javascript	6 months	React Native	1 month
Bootstrap	6 months	HTML/CSS	1 year
MySQL	1 month	UX	HCI Certificate
JAVA	1 month	Adobe CC	2 years